{
 "q2a1": {
   "question": "Which sign is followed in western astrology?",
   "answer": "2",
   "choices": "Moon,Sun,None",
   "correctAnswer": "Sun sign is followed in Western astrology.",
   "relatedLink": "/"
 },
 "q2a2": {
   "question": "What is meant by Rashi?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Moon sign in Vedic Astrology,Sun sign,None",
   "correctAnswer": "Rashi is Moon sign in Vedic Astrology.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/rashi/"
 },
 "q2a3": {
   "question": "Are there Telegram channels on Vedic Astrology?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Yes,No,Do not know",
   "correctAnswer": "There are Telegram channels on Vedic Astrology.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/telegram/"
 },
 "q2a4": {
   "question": "What is Tithi?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "The waxing and waning of moon,Sun Sign,Moon sign",
   "correctAnswer": "The waxing and waning of moon, measured in multiples of 12 degree of the zodiac arc.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/tithi-information/"
 },
 "q2a5": {
   "question": "Who is the best author of books in Vedic Astrology?",
   "answer": "2",
   "choices": "Amateur Mishra,B.V. Raman,None",
   "correctAnswer": "B.V. Raman books on Vedic Astrology are the best.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/vedic-astrology-books/"
 },
 "q2a6": {
   "question": "What is the best Vedic Astrology software?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Jagannatha Hora,AstroSoft,Do not know",
   "correctAnswer": "Jagannatha Hora is the best Vedic Astrology software.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/vedic-astrology-software/"
 },
 "q2a7": {
   "question": "Does Hindu temple have astrological significance?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Yes,No,Do not know",
   "correctAnswer": "Yes, Hindu temples have astrological significance.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/astrology-temple/"
 },
 "q2a8": {
   "question": "What is Bhrigu Bindu used for?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Predictions,It is a Mantra, Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Bhrigu Bindu is used in prediction from a horoscope.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/bhrigu-bindu/"
 },
"q2a9": {
   "question": "How to calculate a vedic astrology birth chart?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Astrology Software,Astronomy, Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Using an Astrology software, one can calculate a vedic astrology birth chart.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/birth-chart/"
 },
"q2a10": {
   "question": "What is meant by Dasha in Vedic Astrology?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Used for timing life events,It is a Mantra ,Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Dasha in Vedic Astrology is used for timing life events.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/dasha/"
 },
"q2a11": {
   "question": "Did W.D.Gann, Investor used Vedic Astrology for analysis of Stock Market?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Yes,No ,Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Yes, His Square of Nine algorithm is connected to Vedic Astrology.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/gann-w-d/"
 },
"q2a12": {
   "question": "What is a graha?",
   "answer": "1",
   "choices": "Planet,Star ,Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Graha is a Planet in Vedic Astrology, from a geo-centric point of view. Sun and Moon are considered as Grahas.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/graha/"
 },
"q2a13": {
   "question": "What is a nakshatra?",
   "answer": "2",
   "choices": "Planet,Star ,Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Nakshatra is a star or a group of stars in Vedic Astrology.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/nakshatras/"
 },
"q2a14": {
   "question": "Is Karma and Vedic Astrology connected?",
   "answer": "2",
   "choices": "No,Yes ,Do not Know",
   "correctAnswer": "Karma is - What you sow is what you reap, based on that is Vedic Astrology on Law of Karma and Dharma.",
   "relatedLink": "/articles/karma-and-astrology/"
 }
}